Ted! Ted! Ted!
What is going on?
Am I dreaming
or am I looking at
head coach
Ted Vincent?
Going out there,
warming up
mid-halftime.
It must be raining
cats and dogs,
cuz I feel
like barking.
Ted,
you're that
leg-broken loser.
Don't tell me
you're actually
thinking of
getting in the game.
You got that right.
You're in
your thirties, man.
What good
is that gonna do?
My team's
valued at over
a billion dollars.
You're just a
worthless cripple.
A billion dollars, huh?
Big deal.
I can single-
handedly steamroll
your entire team.
Your boss
is out of her mind.
And she thinks
you're gonna score
a single point.
What if I score?
What if you score?
Let's make it a bet.
You score one point,
you can slap me
in the face
one time.
But when you don't,
I get to slap the
shit out of you.
Better get you
some ice ready.
Your face is
gonna need it later.
Game's almost lost
and he's
still talking big.
I'm gonna turn his
face into bacon later.
Let's go.
You ready?
Let's do this.
Yeah, Ted!
-Whoa!
-Yeah!
-Let's go, Ted!
He threw
that way too far.
No one's
catching that.
He don't even
know how to play.
He's scared stiff.
You scared him
so bad
he forgot
how to play.
Yeah, I got him.
I got him.
Yes!
Holy guacamole,
the Knights'
quarterback is
scrambling out
into the open field?
I must have eaten
something weird
for breakfast today
because I feel like
I am tripping,
ladies and gentlemen.
A scrambling
quarterback?
Has he
lost his mind?
Boss, thank God
I fired this guy,
cuz he would
have wrecked
our entire team.
Here!
What a wild play.
Nobody even came
close to catching
Ted Vincent, and
he makes a score.